Guide to the International Typographical Union Local 99 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
International Typographical Union Local 99 records
1882-1981
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
3178
3178-001
International Typographical Union. Local 99 (Seattle, Wash.)
60.75 cubic feet
Labor union of Seattle, Washington
Local 99 resulted from mergers in 1974 of various locals whose records are represented here. Seattle (Local 202), and Tacoma (Local 170) are the largest. Bremerton (Local 699), Bellingham (Local 355) and Olympia (Local 142) are also represented in the collection.
Minutes, financial records, correspondence, subject series, court papers.
Open to all interested researchers and members of Local 99.
Aulerich, Robert G. J.; Burnett, Robert E.; Cloud, William R.; Cumby, William E.; Gregory, John C.; Haggbloom, Robert A.; Hanson, Wm. D. (William D.); Litonius, J. M.; Olson, Willard G.; Talbott, Ray; Wartinger, Robert L.
Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); International Typographical Union. Local 142 (Olympia, Wash.); International Typographical Union. Local 170 (Tacoma, Wash.); International Typographical Union. Local 202 (Seattle, Wash.); International Typographical Union. Local 355 (Bellingham, Wash.); International Typographical Union. Local 699 (Bremerton, Wash.); International Typographical Union. Local 99 (Seattle, Wash.)$vArchives
Labor unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor unions$zWashington (State)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records
Labor History; Labor Unions; Publishers and Publishing; Washington (State); Seattle; Tacoma; Olympia; Bellingham
- RECORD GROUP A: LOCAL 99, 1957-1981 (Box-folder 1/1-3/19)
  - SERIES I: ROBERT A. HAGGBLOOM FILES, 1957-1981 (Box-folder 1/1-2/25)
    - Haggbloom, Robert, No title (1 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Haggbloom, Robert, No title (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Haggbloom, Robert, No title (3 of 3), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - International Typographical Union-Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - State Printing Plant- Contract proposals, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Olympia News-Warren's Quick Print, Contracts, Correspondence, etc. (1 of 3), 1965-1979 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Olympia News-Warren's Quick Print, Contracts, Correspondence, etc. (2 of 3), 1965-1979 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Olympia News-Warren's Quick Print, Contracts, Correspondence, etc. (3 of 3), 1965-1979 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council (1 of 4), c. 1960-1981 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council (2 of 4), c. 1960-1981 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council (3 of 4), c. 1960-1981 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Allied Printing Trades Council (4 of 4), c. 1960-1981 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Book Publishing Company, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Washington/Alaska Printing Industries, Inc. - Commercial (1 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Washington/Alaska Printing Industries, Inc. - Commercial (2 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Harris Corporation, McKinsey and Company, and Printing Industries of America. 1976. "A New look at management and profits in the printing industry." [Cleveland, Ohio: Harris Corp.]. (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Tacoma Typographical Union no. 170, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Contract File, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Data Process Information-Professional Data Processing, Inc., 1966-1978 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Department of Labor and Industries, 1974 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Everett Automation Committee (1 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Everett Automation Committee (2 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Handwritten note about: Kotterman 6/21/1974, Snead and scanners (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Job Protection Law Kit, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Report on campaign to enact Citizen Job Protection Ordinance in Tacoma, 1966 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Washington State Legislature, c. 1961-1974 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - News Publishing Company, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - North Kitsap Vocational School, c. 1976 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - 75th Anniversary Diamond Jubilee, 1957 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - Tacoma News Tribune (1 of 3), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Tacoma News Tribune (2 of 3), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Tacoma News Tribune (3 of 3), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Tacoma News Tribune, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Everett Herald- The Daily Herald Company, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - The Bremerton Sun (1 of 3), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - The Bremerton Sun ( 2 of 3), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - The Bremerton Sun (3 of 3), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Bremerton Sun Composing Room (1 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Bremerton Sun Composing Room (2 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Publishers-New Equipment Installation-Work Functions-Discussions (1 of 2), 1974 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Publishers-New Equipment Installation-Work Functions-Discussions (2 of 2), 1974 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - International Typographical Union Committee on Laws, 1978 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Citizen's Job Protection Law Kit, Rats For Hire, 1965 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Seattle Newspapers Unity Meetings, c.1964-1972 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Seattle Newspaper Unity Council (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Seattle Newspaper Unity Council (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Newspaper (1 of 4), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Newspaper (2 of 4), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Newspaper (3 of 4), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Newspaper (4 of 4), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Unity Meeting, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Newspaper Scale Committee, c.1973-1975 (Box-folder 2/25)
  - SERIES II: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION, LOCAL 99 MINUTES, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 3/1-3/19)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, June-September, 1974 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, October-December, 1974 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, January-February, 1975 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, March-April, 1975 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, May-June, 1975 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, July-September, 1975 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, October-November, 1975 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, December, 1975 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, January-March, 1976 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, April-May, 1976 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, June-September, 1976 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, October-December, 1976 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, January-February, 1977 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, March-April, 1977 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, May-July, 1977 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, August-September, 1977 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes, October-December, 1977 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes -- Executive Committee, February-December, 1975 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - International Typographical Union, Local 99, Minutes -- Executive Committee, May-November, 1974 (Box-folder 3/19)
- RECORD GROUP B: INTERNATIONAL TYPOGRAPHICAL UNION LOCAL 202 SEATTLE, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-47/1, 69-73)
  - SERIES I: ORGANIZATION, 1882-1929
    - Constitution and Bylaws of Typographical Union Seattle No. 202, 1891-1906 (Box 66 (Flat box))
    - Constitution and Bylaws:Seattle Typographical No.202 (1882) and includes others: Seattle Photo Engravers Union No.23 (1909), International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union (1916), Pacific Slope Typographical Conference (1920), New York Typographical Union No.6 (1924), Los Angeles Typographical Union No. 174 (1927), Multnomah Typographical Union No. 58 (1928), Chicago Typographical Union No. 17 (1929), 1882-1929 (Box 66 (Flat box))
  - SERIES II: GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE of Administrative Staff, 1908-1978 (Box-folder 4/1-10/51)
    - Organizational Materials, including contracts, by-laws, and commercial shop agreement, 1915-1969 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - International Typographical Union. 1935. A pictorial presentation of the Union Printers Home: erected and maintained by the International Typographical Union at Colorado Springs, Colorado: 1892-1935. Indianapolis, Ind: The Union. (Box-folder 4/2)
    - International Typographical Union. 1935. A pictorial presentation of the Union Printers Home: erected and maintained by the International Typographical Union at Colorado Springs, Colorado: 1892-1935. Indianapolis, Ind: The Union. (Box-folder 4/3)
    - General Correspondence 1908-24, 1908-1924 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Union Printer's Home Behlke, H, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Union Printer's Home Christian, Cecil, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Union Printer's Home Sovereign, JR, 1950 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Union Printer's Home Christensen, Lola, 1950 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Union Printer's Home Peterson, Leo, 1948 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Union Printer's Home Erikson, H I, 1950 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Union Printer's Home McKean, JB, 1950 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Union Printer's Home Berggren J S, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Union Printer's Home Graham, EM, 1948 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Union Printers Home, 1948 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Matheson Donation, 1948 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Union Printer's Home Mulligan, Robert E, 1947 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Union Printers Home Anderson, O L, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Union Printers Home Nolan, F P, 1947 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Union Printers Home De Gork, A, 1947 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Union Printers Home Peterson, Leo M, 1945 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Union Printer's Home, 1944 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Union Printers Home Mooney, Fred, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Union Printer's Home Seibert, EM, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Union Printers Home Day, W. A., 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Union Printers Home Sovereign, James, 1944 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Union Printers Home Robert E. Mulligan, 1945 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Union Printers Home Whitty, LH, 1944 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Union Printers Home Brown, Wm E, 1944 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Union Printers Home Gumaer, CA, 1944 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - Houtchens, R, 1943 (Box-folder 4/30)
    - Union Printers Home Blackford, W. F, 1943 (Box-folder 4/31)
    - Union Printers Home Elsey B F, 1943 (Box-folder 4/32)
    - Union Printers Home Moffett, PJ, 1943 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Union Printers Home Chapman, Bertha, 1943 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Union Printers Home Ashton, JC, 1943 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Union Printers Home McLeland, J, 1942 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - Union Printers Home Anderson, Marie, 1942 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - Union Printers Home Siebert, E, 1942 (Box-folder 4/38)
    - Union Printers Home Berg Otto, 1942 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - Union Printers Home Houtchens, R, 1942 (Box-folder 4/40)
    - Union Printers Home Carothers, F, 1941 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - Union Printers Home Johnson, K, 1940 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - Union Printers Home Christensen, L O, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - Union Printers Home Adela DeGork, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 4/44)
    - union printers home Graham E M, 1940 (Box-folder 4/45)
    - Union Printers Home Richards, RS, 1940 (Box-folder 4/46)
    - Union Printers Home "Brown", 1938 (Box-folder 4/47)
    - Union Printers Home Lyons WC, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 4/48)
    - Union Printers Home Schott CJ, 1934 (Box-folder 4/49)
    - Union Printers Home- Application, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 4/50)
    - Union Printers Home Miller AA, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 4/51)
    - Union Printers Home Swenson, 1933 (Box-folder 4/52)
    - Union Printers Home Turner, 1933 (Box-folder 4/53)
    - International Typographical Union Pres Baker, 1930-1941 (Box-folder 4/54)
    - Pelkey E J International Typographical Union Representative, 1932-1936 (Box-folder 4/55)
    - International Typographical Union President Howard, 1930-1938 (Box-folder 4/56)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Gill, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 4/57)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Hurd #2, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 4/58)
    - International Typographical Union Sec Hurd #3, 1946 (Box-folder 4/59)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Randolph #1, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 4/60)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Randolph #2, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 4/61)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Randolph #3, 1921-1933 (Box-folder 4/62)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Randolph #4 (1 of 2), 1939-1944 (Box-folder 4/63)
    - International Typographical Union Secretary Randolph #4 (2 of 2), 1939-1944 (Box-folder 4/64)
    - Seattle Typographical Union Secretary Cloud, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 4/65)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President Mesegee, 1928-1941 (Box-folder 4/66)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President and Secretary McCullough, 1909-1935 (Box-folder 4/67)
    - Pres. McParland, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 4/68)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President Garrison, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 4/69)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President Hickey, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/70)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President Lewis, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 4/71)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President Roush, 1952-1955 (Box-folder 4/72)
    - Seattle Typographical Union President McGlothlin, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 4/73)
    - Rowbottom, Robert- Union Printers Home, 1955 (Box-folder 4/74)
    - Stark, Ray- Union Printers Home, 1953 (Box-folder 4/75)
    - Dibb, RI- Union Printers Home, 1955 (Box-folder 4/76)
    - Graham, EM- Union Printers Home, 1935 (Box-folder 4/77)
    - Sheppard, PC Union Printers Home, 1955 (Box-folder 4/78)
    - Hanson, HM Union Printers Home, 1955 (Box-folder 4/79)
    - Chance, Ollie, 1948-1955 (Box-folder 4/80)
    - Adamson, PJ, 1952 (Box-folder 4/81)
    - Reich, George, 1951 (Box-folder 4/82)
    - Cloud, D. Gerald, 1949 (Box-folder 4/83)
    - Seibert, EM Union Printers Home, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 4/84)
    - Shoemaker, AC, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/85)
    - Ad for International Typograhical Union including World's Greatest Home for Aged and Infirm Printers, c. 1950s (Box-folder 4/86)
    - Pres. Wartinger LandD Trustee, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Eighth Annual Report to the Trustees of STU-Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1968 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Ninth Annual Report to the Trustees of STU- Employer Life and Disability Fund, 1969 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Typographical Union-Employer Pension Plan: Annual Report of the Actuary, 1967 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - STU Employer Life and Disability Fund Financial Statements ending June 30, 1970, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Financial Records, 1970 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Trustee- Pension, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Seattle Typographical Union- Financial Statement, 1969 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Typographical Union- Employer Pension Plan, 1966 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Life and Disability Statements, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Apprenticeship Council, 1971 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Changes in the Laws: Adopted by the One Hundred Seventieth Convention, 1975 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Apprentices, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Times-P.I. Glossies, 1967 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Racial Questions, etc., 1970 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Frayn Printing Company, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Conference newsletters and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - History of the International Typographical Union Libraries, 1965 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Health and Welfare Committee, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Seattle Post Intelligencer, Los Angeles Times Strike, 1968 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Unity Committee, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - Allied Label Problems, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - International Typographical Union Training Center, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Contracts, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Commercial Proposal, 1971 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Politics, etc., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Miscellaneous International Typographical Union, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association Agreement and sheets of 'Delete' and 'Same As Old Contract' markers, c. 1968 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Contract Files, 1969 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - Health and Welfare, 1971 (Box-folder 5/31)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Law State and Federal, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Group Health, 1970 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Health and Welfare Med-Sury Information, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Future Negotiation Ammunition, 1960-1972 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - 202, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 5/37)
    - 1971 Negotiation, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Negotiation Ammo. '71 Commercial, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/39)
    - No. 1 Unity Meetings, 1971 (Box-folder 5/40)
    - Joint Negotiation Sessions May 17th, 1971 No. 2 (Box-folder 5/41)
    - San Francisco Info and Sam Kagel Negotiations, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 5/42)
    - Craft Unity Meetings, 1971 (Box-folder 5/43)
    - Color and Engraving- Seattle Times- Post Intelligencer, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 5/44)
    - University of Washington Daily Newspaper, 1970 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - University of Washington -State Mediation etc. Burnett notes, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - University Printing, 1929-1977 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Washington Survey, 1936-1978 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Western Typographers advertisements, Undated (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Bureau of Contract Old, c.1960-1965 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Bureau of Education, 1947-1975 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Membership Statistics, 1937-1975 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - International Typographical Union Officers Correspondence (Contains corresondence between local 99 and Colorado headquarters), c.1951-1977 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - University of Washington-Reimbursement of overpayment of dues paid on sick leave, c.1960's (Box-folder 6/10)
    - International Typographical Union Officers Correspondence (Contains corresondence between local 99 and Colorado headquarters), 1957-1976 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Walt Marvick, c.1950-1970 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - F.E. McGlothilin, 1958-1977 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - R.L. Wartinger, 1970 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - International Representative, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - Assistant Talbott, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - International Typographical Union Assessment, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - International Typographical Union Training Center Correspondence, c.1956-1971 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - International Typographical Union reproduction survey, 1960 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Seattle Newspaper Publishers Association, 1959-1976 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - J.M. Stangler-Arbitration, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Diane Freethy-5 Man Board, 1973 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - James Bonn Arbitration, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Art Schmidt vs. Graphic Arts Center, 1970 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Arbitration Hardenbrooke, 1961 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Arbitration-Seattle Times Substitutions (Part 1), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Arbitration-Seattle Times Substitutions (Part 2), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Armitage-Times Standing Committee Case, 1969 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Standing Committee, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Stereotypers, c.1950-1964 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Signed Stipulations Commercial, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Stipulations-1964, c.1960-1965 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Stipulations, 1952-1960 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - United Labor Advisory Committee, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - United States Department of Labor Union Wage Survey #1, 1959-1976 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - United States Labor Union Wage (?) (Part 1), c.1959-1974 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - United States Labor Union Wage (?) (Part 2), c.1959-1974 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - G.I. Apprentices, c.1949-1975 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Washington State Apprenticeship Council, 1959-1977 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - Washington State and Other Typographical Conferences 19??-1965, 1956-1977 (Box-folder 7/20)
    - Washington State and Other Typographical Conferences 1965-1966 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - Washington State and Other Typographical Conferences 1967, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - National Labor Relations Board 1965, Grocery Boys, etc. (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Grocery Boys-National Labor Relations Board and Legal Action 1965, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - National Labor Relations Board Case Number 19-CC-278 Seattle Typographical Union Number 202-Central Publishing Company, Incorporated, 1965 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - News Publishing-National Labor Relations Board, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - News Publishing vs. Photoengravers National Labor Relations Board, 1967 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - National Labor Relations Board Case Number 19-CD-126, Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union Local 23P (News Publishing Company) Hearing dates July 12, 13, 1967 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - International Typographical Union-International Printing Pressmen Jurisdictional Dispute, 1957 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - International Typographical Union-International Printing Pressmen National Labor Relations Board Case Number 19-RC-2002, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - International Printing Pressmen's Union National Labor Relations Board, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - New Process School, 1956-1974 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - New Process Committee, 1958-1977 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Organization, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - President Robert Aulerich Correspondence, c.1974-1979 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Organization New York Printing Utilities Branch, International Typographical Union, Local 6, c.1956-1972 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Pension Plan Texts, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Pension-Mickey International Typographical Union, 1948-1972 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Portland Reporter Employee Stock Purchase, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - National Labor Relations Board-Lithographers and Photoengravers, Local 23-P v. Buyer's Guide, News Publishing Company, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Printing Industry of Seattle Incorporated, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Printing Industry of Seattle, Part 1, c.1939-1976 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - Printing Industry of Seattle, Part 2, c.1939-1976 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Printing Industry of Seattle, Part 3, c.1939-1976 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Professional Data Processing, Incorporated, 1965-1979 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Resolutions, 1950-1974 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Rodents ["Rats"; Non-Union Contractors], c.1921-1937 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Scott Publishing Company vs. International Typographical Union, et al., 1959 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Tacoma News Tribune Grievance Committee, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Laws Committee 1929-1953, c.1937-1952 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - B.C. Typo Bulletin, 1954-1968 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Doozerdoo, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Newspapers, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Financial Statements, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 9/6)